topeleven.com 2017-06-28

# Privacy Policy - Top Eleven be a Football Manager

## Nordeus Privacy & Cookie Policy

Valid from 07 Jul 2017.

## Nordeus Privacy Policy

**A quick summary:**

 **1\. This document explains what information is collected regarding the Nordeus games and services.  
2\. It also explains how we use that information, where we store it and how we protect it.  
3\. We can share the information with partners for the purpose of providing the Nordeus Services.  
4\. We will not share your information for third party advertising purposes.  
5\. We explain your rights in relation to the information.**

This Privacy Policy explains to you how your personal information is collected and stored and what happens to it regarding the Nordeus Services. Because we know legal wording is not much fun, we have included a short and informal summary of each section (but the full version is the legally binding one). If you have any queries you can contact us at support@nordeus.com. 

We’d also like to remind you that our Nordeus User Agreement has more information about how we operate the [Nordeus Services](http://www.topeleven.com/terms-facebook/ "Terms of Use").

### 1\. WHO WE ARE AND WHAT THIS PRIVACY POLICY GOVERNS

This Privacy Policy explains the different kinds of information Nordeus can collect from you when you’re using the Nordeus Services. Legally, we cannot and will not collect personal information about children below 13 without parental/guardian involvement. We will comply with applicable privacy laws.

We can change this Privacy Policy, but if we do we will put the changed version online and normally it will take effect 30 days afterwards. Please feel free to contact us if you have any questions with regards to the changes. 

1.1. Who is Nordeus? We are Nordeus Limited, incorporated and registered in Ireland with company number 526421 having an address at Nordeus Limited, 3rd Floor, Kilmore House, Park Lane, Spencer Dock, Dublin 1, Ireland and its group of companies (“Nordeus”).

1.2. Which services does this Privacy Policy apply to? This Privacy Policy applies to our video games including Spellsouls: Duel of Legends and Top Eleven, our websites (including but not limited to www.Nordeus.com), plus all other Nordeus products and services, including (but not limited to) user accounts, customer and technical support, official forums, wikis, blogs and social media services (we will just refer to “Nordeus Services” to cover all these things).

1.3. What information does this Privacy Policy apply to? Specifically, this Privacy Policy governs personal information (or, in the USA, personally identifiable information) and non-personal information (or, in the USA, non-personally identifiable information), which we collect from you when you are using the Nordeus Services (“personal information” means information, which, on its own or in combination with other information, can be used to identify you).

1.4. What about children? We recognise we have a special obligation to protect personal information obtained from children. We do not and will not knowingly collect personal information from any child under the age of 13 without consent from their parent or guardian. If you are a parent or guardian and are concerned about the transfer of personal information about your child, please contact support@nordeus.com.

1.5. Will we ever change this Privacy Policy? We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time, for example to reflect changes in our services or to reflect applicable laws. If we do, we will make the changed Privacy Policy available online, make reasonable efforts to notify you of this and update the “Last Updated” date. Once we change the Privacy Policy, it will become legally binding on you 30 days after we post it online. During that period, you are welcome to contact us if you have specific questions about the changes at support@nordeus.com. If you do not agree to those changes (regardless of whether you email us), then unfortunately we must ask you to cease using all Nordeus Services: in order to make the Nordeus Services work properly we need to have everyone using them under the same rules instead of different people having different rules. 

1.6. We respect your right to privacy and will only process personal information in accordance with applicable legislation in the EU, the USA and elsewhere. For personal information contained in this Privacy Policy which is used by Nordeus in connection with the Nordeus Services, Nordeus is the data controller under European Union data protection legislation.

### 2\. WHAT INFORMATION IS COVERED?

We may collect certain information when you use the Nordeus Services such as your name and email address (more information below). We do not receive or store your payment details. Please also read our Cookie Policy below.

2.1. What information might we collect from you? When you sign up for, download, use or play the Nordeus Services then we will collect certain information from you. This information may include:

i. Your name;  
ii. Your date of birth;  
iii. Your email address;  
iv. Any user name used to identify yourself;  
v. Details of your digital platform account;  
vi. Any other information which you supply us via our services (including the content of messages sent using any chat / communications systems);  
vii. Technical details about any device which you use to access our services, including: Internet and/or network connection (including IP address); any mobile device identifier; your operating system, browser type or other software; or your hardware or other technical details. This is technical data about our users and their actions and patterns which does not provide personal information;  
viii. Details of your use of our services including, but not limited to: metrics information about when and how you use the services; traffic data; and your geographical location data;  
ix. If/when we decide to deploy social networking features in any of the Nordeus Services, and if you link our services to a social networking account(s), then we may collect details about your use of social networking account(s) and our services). This may potentially include certain information from (for example) Facebook or other social networks (including access to your name, location, gender, birth date, email address, photo, profile URL and friends list as well as aggregated non-personal analytics data about our users) strictly in accordance with the social network(s)’ terms and conditions; and  
x. Other information required in order to help you with any queries or support matters.  
Some of the information types referred to above may be collected on an aggregated or anonymised (e.g. hashed) basis, or we may use it or share it in an aggregated or anonymised way, for research or analysis into the way our services operate and are used.

2.2. What about the storage of payment details? The processing and storage of payment details is a matter for the relevant platform and payment method/processor. Nordeus will not receive, process or store any of your payment details. This is because the payment transactions themselves are completed through the relevant platforms (e.g. Apple’s App Store or Google Play) via the personal email address you have associated with that platform account. If you make in-game purchases within the Nordeus Services, we are notified by the payment processor once a transaction takes place, but we will not receive any of your actual payment details. 

2.3. What about cookies? We also collect information about you via cookies. You can find out more about our use of cookies in our Cookie Policy below. The Cookie Policy forms part of this Privacy Policy. 

### 3\. HOW IS INFORMATION COLLECTED FROM YOU?

We will collect information ourselves or via third parties for appropriate matters.

How might we collect this information from you? Information may be collected or processed regarding you in the following ways: (a) information you give us via the Nordeus Services; (b) information given when you contact us or report a problem with the Nordeus Services; and (c) we may also ask you to complete surveys that we use for research purposes, although you don’t have to respond to them. We may collect this information via the Nordeus Services or trusted third parties connected with us for optional things like surveys or polls.

### 4\. WHERE IS YOUR INFORMATION STORED?

We will store your information in the European Economic Area. We will do our best to keep this information secure. No information security system is perfect so please remember to be careful.

Where will your information be stored? The information we hold will be stored and processed in the European Economic Area. By submitting your personal information, you agree to such transfer, storing or processing. We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that this information is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

All information we hold is stored on our secure servers (which we own or license from appropriate third parties). We use industry standard procedures and security standards to prevent unauthorised access to our servers, however no online service or website can be completely secure, so please protect the account information in your possession as well.

### 5\. HOW IS YOUR INFORMATION STORED?

We will use your information to run, maintain and improve the Nordeus Services as well as to communicate with you (e.g. with newsletters or emails).

Sometimes we may share anonymised, non-personal information like operating system types with partners in order to run our services.

5.1. How might your information be used? Your information may be used in the following ways:

i. To ensure that the Nordeus Services are presented in the most effective manner for you and for your device from which you access them;  
ii. To provide you with marketing information, products or services that you request from us and which we feel may interest you – for example, we may send you newsletters or emails about the Nordeus Services (of course, it’s optional and we will ask you for permission first where required);  
iii. To carry out our obligations arising from any contracts between you and us;  
iv. To allow you to participate in interactive features of the Nordeus Services when you choose to do so;  
v. To notify you about changes to the Nordeus Services;  
vi. To provide, maintain, protect and improve the Nordeus Services and to protect Nordeus and other Nordeus Services users;  
vii. To provide you with player to play chat functionality and other communication systems (Nordeus reserves the right to monitor the content of any of your messages and prevent your use of any such chat or other communication systems for any reason);  
viii. To comply with intellectual property protection obligations we have under applicable laws including the Digital Millennium Copyright Act and the E-Commerce Directive; and  
ix. To assess the performance of the Nordeus Services.

5.2. Will we ever share any of your information with other parties? We may share some aggregated and general non-personal information on user behaviour (e.g. sales per region) with our partners who work with us to provide the Nordeus Services to you (for example, with payment providers) in order to support, improve or amend the Nordeus Services. We may also share non-personal information with data analysis services to help us run the Nordeus Services.

### 6\. HOW YOU USE YOUR INFORMATION AND THIRD PARTIES?

You have the option to share your own personal information with others parties, in which case it will be governed by those parties’ own privacy policies – make sure to take a look at them. 

Please remember that any communications you have via the Nordeus Services may reveal details about you. Also, any information you post publicly will be publicly available to other people. We are not responsible for your use of any otherwise private personal information which you make available, or the activities of other users or other third parties to whom you give or make available your information or content. The Nordeus Services may, from time to time, contain or connect you with third party content or services. Our Privacy Policy does not extend to external sites or companies, so please refer directly to their privacy policies.

### 7\. OTHER MATTERS

See below for a few miscellaneous data matters… 

7.1. Please be aware that we are subject to various laws and we may be required to release personal information in order to comply with law enforcement or other legal requirements.

7.2. In the unlikely event of a reorganisation or merger of Nordeus we may transfer personal information to an involved third party who will protect this to at least the same level as we do in this Privacy Policy.

### 8\. YOUR RIGHTS

You have rights about how your personal information is used, which can vary depending on where you live. If you have any questions, please contact us at support@nordeus.com.

8.1. Can you ask us to stop processing your personal information? You have the right to ask us not to process your personal information for marketing purposes. You can change your email settings to unsubscribe from email communications.

8.2. Can you see what information we store for you? Depending on where you live, you may have additional privacy rights. For example, in the EU you have the right to access your personal information we possess; you may have the legal right to contact us to request that we delete your personal information from our system; and you may have the legal right to ask us to rectify/correct your personal information if appropriate. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to honour your request, but we may decline requests that are unreasonably repetitive, are disproportionate or infringe the privacy of others. 

8.3. Under California law, California residents who have an established business relationship with us have the right to request certain information with respect to the types of personal information we have shared with third parties for their direct marketing purposes, and the identities of those third parties, within the immediately preceding calendar year, subject to certain exceptions. All requests for such information must be in writing and sent to: Nordeus Limited, 3rd Floor, Kilmore House, Park Lane, Spencer Dock, Dublin 1, Ireland. This same California law permits us to provide you, in response to your written request, with a cost-free means to choose not to have your information shared rather than providing the above described information. You may exercise that choice by contacting us at the address above.

8.4. Who should you contact if you would like to exercise these rights? If you would like to exercise any of these rights or have any queries regarding them, please contact: support@nordeus.com.

## Nordeus Cookie Policy

We (meaning Nordeus Limited) use technologies in our video games including Spellsouls: Duel of Legends and Top Eleven, our websites (including but not limited to www.Nordeus.com), plus all other Nordeus products and services, including (but not limited to) user accounts, customer and technical support, official forums, wikis, blogs and social media services (which we’ll call the “Services”) to collect information that helps us improve your online experience. We refer to these technologies, which include cookies, collectively as “cookies.” This policy explains the different types of cookies used on the Services and how you can control them.  
We hope that this policy helps you understand and feel more confident about our use of cookies. If you have any further queries, please contact us at support@nordeus.com.  
Please also see our Privacy Policy above and our [User Agreement](http://www.topeleven.com/terms-facebook/ "Terms of Use").

1\. By accessing or using the Services you authorise us to collect certain technical information in order to (i) analyse usage of the Services; (ii) provide a more personalised experience; and (iii) manage advertising. We, and our third party service providers, may use server log files or web log files and tracking technologies to collect and analyse certain types of technical information, including but not limited to, cookies, IP addresses, device type, device identifiers, browser types, browser language, URLs, domain names, landing pages, game state, the date and time of usage of the Services, and other similar information.

2\. We may also use other technologies, including but not limited to, web bugs, tracking pixels and cookies. Web bugs allow us to know if a certain page was visited or whether an email was opened, while tracking pixels allow us to advertise more efficiently by excluding current users from certain promotional messages, identifying the source of a new installation or delivering ads to you on other websites. Cookies allow us to improve the quality of the Services, make recommendations, and make the Services easier to use for you. A cookie is a small text file recorded on your hard drive that identifies you as a unique user and contains certain information about your particular login session and/or your use of the Services. Please note that companies delivering advertisements within the Services may also use cookies or other technologies, and those practices are subject to their own policies.

3\. We use Facebook’s Custom Audience feature to target users with advertising from time to time. Custom Audiences allow us to target ads to a specific set of people through Facebook. You can manage your privacy settings in the privacy tab of your Facebook account.

4\. Regarding the Nordeus websites including www.topeleven.com, www.nordeus.com and www.spellsouls.com.

a. These sites use Google Analytics including its Remarketing feature based on Display Advertising (www.google.com/analytics/) for online advertising and for website analytics purposes – meaning that we use them to see how many visitors come to our site, the pages that generate interest and the links that visitors most often click on (amongst other things). Google Analytics uses cookies – small text files that are placed on your computer that store certain limited information about you. The cookies we use do not enable any visitor to our site to be individually identified and will only be used for online advertising and website analytics purposes. You can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize Google Display Network ads using the Ads Preferences Manager.

b. In addition, the sites mentioned above use cookies, flash cookies, web beacons and similar technologies to collect information about you. This enables us to tailor our service offering (including our sites) to provide you with products and services which are more relevant to your individual tastes. We and third-party vendors, including Google, use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookie) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) together to inform, optimize, and serve ads based on your past visits to our sites. Third-party vendors, including Google, show our ads on sites across the Internet. You may change your website browser settings to reject cookies, although please note that if you do this it may impair the functionality of our sites. For further information about cookies, including how to refuse cookies, please visit www.allaboutcookies.org.

5\. We may change this Cookie Policy at any time: please take a look at the “LAST UPDATED” date at the top of this policy to see when it was last revised. Any amendments to this Cookie Policy will come into effect a reasonable period of time after this “LAST UPDATED” date (normally we consider 30 days to be a reasonable time period) unless you contact us before that date to discuss or query any of the amendments. 

## Nordeus Privacy & Cookie Policy

Valid until 06 Jul 2017.

We are committed to protecting Your Information and providing You with a safe, efficient and customised experience. To this effect, We have created this Privacy Policy to let You know what Information We collect when You use the Services, why We collect this Information and how We use the collected Information. The defined terms used in this Privacy Policy shall have the same meaning as specified in the Terms of Service.

### 1\. ABOUT THIS PRIVACY POLICY (the “Privacy Policy” or the “Policy”)

1.1. This Policy represents an agreement between you (“ **You** ” or “ **Your** ”) and Nordeus Limited, 3rd floor, Kilmore House, Park Lane Spencer Dock, Dublin 1, Ireland (“ **Nordeus** ”, “ **We** ”, “ **Us** ” or “ **Our** ”). This Policy sets out the ways that We use the personal information which we may gather in providing you with games, software, updates, add-ons (including virtual goods and virtual currency) and services that are offered to you by us as well as any Nordeus website which you access to avail of any of the above (collectively, the “ **Services** ”). 

1.2. References to Nordeus in these Terms shall include any Nordeus affiliates which shall include subsidiaries, parent companies and any other entities under common ownership. Where you receive or participate in a Service provided directly by Nordeus, Nordeus is the data controller of your personal data.

1.3. Our Services may be accessed through one or more third party websites, services or platforms (such as Facebook or the App Store). In addition, payments are processed through third party payment processors (for example, through a third party service or platform which you are using to access the Services, such as Facebook). Our Services may also contain links to other websites and services. Any information that you provide on or to a third-party website or service is provided directly to the owner of the website or service and is subject to that party’s privacy policy. Our Privacy Policy does not apply to such websites or services and we’re not responsible for the content, privacy or security practices and policies of those websites or services. To protect your Information we recommend that you carefully review the privacy policies of other websites and services that you access.

### 2\. AGREEING TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

2.1. By accessing or using the Services, You are agreeing to the terms of this Privacy Policy. This is Our entire and exclusive Privacy Policy and it supersedes any earlier version.

2.2. This Privacy Policy should be read in conjunction with Our Terms of Service and any additional applicable terms brought to your attention when You access the Services. Where you access and use the Services, you will also be bound by our Terms of Service.

2.3. We reserve the right to amend this Privacy Policy at any time and You shall be notified of any such amendment via the platform through which You access the Services and/or by Us publishing the modified Privacy Policy on any platform through which You access the Services. We recommend that You revisit this Privacy Policy on a regular basis. For the avoidance of doubt, Your continued use of the Services shall be interpreted as deemed acceptance of any modifications to the Privacy Policy.

2.4. If You have any questions regarding the Privacy Policy, visit our Support Centre at support.nordeus.eu

### 3\. HOW WE COLLECT INFORMATION 

3.1. Depending on the nature of the Services which You use, We will, in accordance with this Privacy Policy, collect information and/or personal data, including but not limited to, Your first and last name, gender, date of birth, profile picture or its URL, residential address, email address, phone number or other contact information and certain technical information.

3.2. We will also collect:

  * Your screen name (user ID);
  * Technical or other details about any device which you use to access the Services: Internet and/or network connection (including your IP address, Media Access Control (MAC), operating system, browser type or other software); hardware (including computer hardware or mobile model); mobile device details (including your mobile device type and number; mobile carrier details; and unique device identifier) or other technical details. 
  * Details of your use of the Services including, but not limited to: traffic data, location/geographical data, the Service resources that you access, the time you spend on the Services, crash reports and reasons for connection drops.
  * Data that you provide to Us via any third party website, application or service (including Facebook or Google) which You use to access the Services or which you make publicly available on such third party website or service, or which you give Us via any forms on the website www.topeleven.com (or any other Nordeus or Top Eleven website), by text message, via player forums, data stored in Services log files or by contacting Us. 
  * Information provided when you report a problem with any of the Services.
  * We may also ask you to complete surveys that We use for research purposes, although you do not have to respond to them.

The information set out in sections 3.1 and 3.2 is collectively the “ **Information** ” insofar as it is information which is capable of identifying You.

3.3. By accessing or using the Services, You are authorising Us to collect, store and use Your Information. You can control the amount of Information You are authorising Us to collect, store and use by altering Your privacy settings on the mobile device, platform or service through which you access the Services. You can find out more about these settings, and how to control them, on the mobile device, platform or service from which You access the Services.

3.4. We may collect, store and use in accordance with this Privacy Policy certain Information where You provide such Information either (i) directly to Us; or (ii) through Your use of a third party platform or service, which may, with your permission, provide this Information to Us through its application programming interface. We may also receive Information from Our third party service providers. We will have access to any Information You provide to such third party service providers. We will use that Information to provide you with the Services and as otherwise set out in this Privacy Policy.

3.5. By accessing or using the Services via Your mobile phone, or other mobile device, You are authorising Us to collect its unique device identifier and IP address. We may also collect the name You have associated with Your mobile phone or other mobile device, device type, telephone number, country, and any other information You choose to provide. We may also access Your contacts to enable You to invite friends to join You on the Services if you request that we do this on your behalf.

3.6. We receive and store the information that You provide, including Your telephone number, when You sign up to and consent to having text messages sent directly to Your mobile phone. These text messages notify You of in-game activity within the Services and may allow You to access the Services from Your mobile device.

3.7. Should You purchase a licence to use Virtual Items through a third party platform, and that purchase is processed by or on behalf of a third party (e.g. Apple Inc. where You have made a purchase on an iOS device), We may receive payment information which You provide to that third party but only in order to allow us to provide you with the licence to use Virtual Items. Any purchases which You make through a third party in this manner may be subject to their policies and it is Your sole responsibility to ensure Your compliance with those policies. We do not collect, nor do we have access to any of your billing or credit information. That data is collected and stored by third party payment service providers (for example, the platform through which you are accessing the Services).

### 4\. HOW WE USE INFORMATION

4.1. We use information held about you in some of the following ways:

  * To provide you with the Services.
  * To ensure that content from Our Services is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer or other device from which you access the Services.
  * To provide you with information or services that you request from Us or which We feel may interest you, if you have consented to be contacted for such purposes. 
  * To perform Our obligations under any contracts entered into with you.
  * To allow you to participate in interactive features of Our Services, if you choose.
  * To notify you about changes to Our Services.
  * To provide you with support and other administrative services.
  * To prevent fraud and provide safe and secure Services.
  * To provide you with targeted advertising.
  * To comply with our own legal obligations.

4.2. Where you access the Services as an App or through a third party platform such as Facebook, we may from time to time send you “push notifications” provided that you have allowed us to do so in accordance with the settings on your mobile device. You can manage push notifications within the settings of your mobile device.

4.3. Please remember that using the Services may reveal information relating to you which is publicly available on the platform that you are using to access the Services (for example, your screen name, your profile picture and the content of your publicly available communications to other users). 

4.4. We are not responsible for the activities of other users or other third parties to whom you choose to provide your personal information (whether via Our Services or otherwise).

4.5. If your account on our Services is closed, we are obliged to store the Information which is saved in our database for a period of time to allow us to comply with applicable laws. Please note that it is not possible to delete Your Information prior to the expiry of applicable statutory retention periods and in order for us to comply with our legal obligations.

4.6. We may disclose Your Information, and the contents of all Your online communications, if required to do so by law, or if We believe in good faith that such action is necessary to: (i) comply with any applicable laws or regulations or any legal process served on Us, the Services or in circumstances where We are under a substantially similar legal obligation; (ii) protect and defend Our rights or property; (iii) act to protect the personal safety of users of the Services or the public; or (iv) if, in Our sole determination, You are found to have cheated or attempted to defraud Us or any other user of the Services in any way, or if We suspect You of any fraudulent activity.

4.7. We may further provide Your Information to any third parties and data processors providing services to Us, including but not limited to, payment processing, data analysis, email delivery, customer service, hosting and marketing services, and by helping us to administer and provide the Services. We take measures to ensure that Our arrangements with third party service providers and data processors protect the privacy of Your Information and that such third parties do not use Your Information for any other purpose than to provide services to Us. 

4.8. We may share Your Information with third party service providers and data processors with regards to promoting their services. You can contact us any time you want to withdraw from these promotional services. We will not actively share Your Information with third party advertisers for their direct marketing purposes unless You give Us Your consent. We may, however, share (i) aggregated information (information about You and other users collectively, but not specifically identifiable to You); (ii) anonymous information; and (iii) certain technical information to develop and deliver targeted advertising in the Services and on the websites of third parties. We may also allow advertisers to collect these types of information within the Services by using tracking technologies like browser cookies and web beacons. Our collection, use, and disclosure of anonymous or aggregated information are not subject to any of the restrictions in this Privacy Policy.

4.9. The Services support and may encourage interaction among users. Access to your username may allow other users to view the public information associated with your related account and to communicate with you through the related social network communication channels.

4.10. You may be offered the option of importing Your contact list or address book contacts, either automatically or manually, into the Services in order to enable You to (i) locate any of Your contacts who are also users of the Services; and/or (ii) invite Your contacts to become users of the Services. Should You opt to import Your contact list or address book contacts, You are authorising Us to store Your contact details on Our databases for these purposes, unless You expressly revoke this authorisation. For the avoidance of doubt, any passwords which You provide to Us to facilitate this import shall not be stored by Us.

4.11. You may contact Us by visiting our Support Centre at support.nordeus.eu if You: (i) want to confirm the accuracy of the Information We have collected about You; (ii) would like to update Your Information; and/or (iii) have any complaint regarding Our use of Your Information. If requested, We will (x) update Your Information, provided that You provide evidence as We may reasonably require for such changes, or (y) mark any Information to prohibit future use for marketing purposes. 

4.12. For the avoidance of doubt, nothing in this Privacy Policy shall prevent Us from retaining Your Information where We are required to do so by law. If You have sent or posted content on the Service, We may not be able to delete it.

### 5\. COOKIES AND AUTOMATED INFORMATION COLLECTION

5.1. By accessing or using the Services You authorise Us to collect certain technical information in order to (i) analyse usage of the Services; (ii) provide a more personalised experience; and (iii) manage advertising. We, and our third party service providers, may use server log files or web log files and tracking technologies to collect and analyse certain types of technical information, including but not limited to, cookies, IP addresses, device type, device identifiers, browser types, browser language, URLs, domain names, landing pages, game state, the date and time of usage of the Service, and other similar information.

5.2. We may also use other technologies, including but not limited to, web bugs, tracking pixels and cookies. Web bugs allow Us to know if a certain page was visited or whether an email was opened, while tracking pixels allow Us to advertise more efficiently by excluding current users from certain promotional messages, identifying the source of a new installation or delivering ads to You on other websites. Cookies allow Us to improve the quality of the Services, make recommendations, and make the Services easier to use for You. A cookie is a small text file recorded on Your hard drive that identifies You as a unique user and contains certain information about Your particular login session and/or Your use of the Services. Please note that companies delivering advertisements within the Services may also use cookies or other technologies, and those practices are subject to their own policies.

5.3. We use Facebook’s Custom Audience feature to target users with advertising from time to time. Custom Audiences allow us to target ads to a specific set of people through Facebook. You can manage your privacy settings in the privacy tab of your Facebook account. 

5.4. In the case the websites www.topeleven.com and www.nordeus.com:

(i) These sites uses Google Analytics including its Remarketing feature based on Display Advertising (www.google.com/analytics/) for online advertising and for website analytics purposes – meaning that We use them to see how many visitors come to Our Site, the pages that generate interest and the links that visitors most often click on (amongst other things). Google Analytics uses cookies – small text files that are placed on your computer that store certain limited information about you. The cookies we use do not enable any visitor to Our Site to be individually identified and will only be used for online advertising and website analytics purposes. You can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize Google Display Network ads using the Ads Preferences Manager.

(ii) In addition, the sites mentioned above use cookies, flash cookies, web beacons and similar technologies to collect information about you. This enables Us to tailor Our service offering (including Our Site) to provide you with products and services which are more relevant to your individual tastes. We and third-party vendors, including Google, use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookie) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) together to inform, optimize, and serve ads based on your past visits to Our Site. Third-party vendors, including Google, show our ads on sites across the Internet. You may change your website browser settings to reject cookies, although please note that if you do this it may impair the functionality of Our Site. For further information about cookies, including how to refuse cookies, please visit www.allaboutcookies.org.

In order to see more details about cookies click here.

### 6\. PROTECTION OF MINORS

6.1. The Services provided by Nordeus (including the game Top Eleven) may only be used by a person over the age of 16 or a person between the age of 13 and 16 where that person’s parent or guardian has reviewed and consents to the Terms and this Policy on their behalf. Any person who provides Information to Nordeus through any part of the Services represents to Nordeus that they are 16 years of age or older or that they are between 13 years of age and 16 years of age and their parent or guardian has reviewed the Terms and this Policy and has consented on their behalf. 

### 7\. SAFETY MEASURES TO PROTECT YOUR INFORMATION

7.1. We take reasonable measures to protect the Information that we collect from or about you (including your personally identifiable information) from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. Please be aware, however, that no method of transmitting information over the Internet or storing information is completely secure. Accordingly, we cannot guarantee the absolute security of any information.

### 8\. DISCLAIMER

8.1. You expressly agree that the Services are provided on an “as is” basis without warranties of any kind. We are not responsible for events beyond Our direct control. Because of the complex and constantly changing nature of Our technology and business, We cannot guarantee, nor do We represent, that there will be an error-free performance regarding the privacy of Your Information, and We will not be liable for any indirect, incidental, consequential or punitive damages relating to the use or release of Your Information.

### 9\. INTERNATIONAL TRANSFERS

9.1. Your Information collected by Us may be stored and processed in any country in which We or Our affiliates, suppliers, ESPs or agents maintain facilities (see section 4.6). By using the Service, You expressly consent to any transfer of Information outside of Your country (including to third countries outside the EEA that may not have been assessed as having adequate privacy laws). 

### 10\. MERGERS AND OTHER EVENTS REQUIRING TRANSFER

10.1. If We should ever file for bankruptcy, or become insolvent, or be acquired by a third party, merge with a third party, sell all or part of Our assets, or transfer substantially all or part of Our relevant assets to a third party, We are entitled to share Your Information You have provided through the Services to potential and subsequent business and merger partners. By agreeing to the Terms of Service, You give Your consent to such transfer of this Information.

### 11\. YOUR RIGHTS

11.1. The following applies only to the processing of Your personal data (i.e. personally identifiable information) by Nordeus in the provision of the Services:

(i) You have the right to ask Us not to process your personal information for marketing purposes (opt-out). We will usually inform you (before collecting your data) if we intend to use your data for such purposes. You can exercise this right by contacting Our Helpcenter at support.nordeus.eu/home.

(ii) You can contact Our Helpcenter at support.nordeus.eu/home to request that We provide you with access to your personal information or that We update or delete your personal information from Our database. We may retain an archived copy of your records if required to do so by law or for legitimate business purposes (for example, where deletion of your personal data from our database may severely disrupt or disable your use of Services).

### 12\. DO NOT TRACK SIGNALS

If you are a California based user of the Services, please note that there is no consensus on how companies like ours should interpret “Do Not Track” signals in the context of recent amendments to the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We do not currently respond to Do Not Track signals, whether that signal is received on a computer or on a mobile device. You can learn more about Do Not Track here: http://www.allaboutdnt.com/.

This post is also available in: [French](http://www.topeleven.com/fr/privacy-facebook/), [German](http://www.topeleven.com/de/privacy-facebook/), [Italian](http://www.topeleven.com/it/privacy-facebook/), [Russian](http://www.topeleven.com/ru/privacy-facebook/), [Spanish](http://www.topeleven.com/es/privacy-facebook/), [Portuguese (Brazil)](http://www.topeleven.com/pt-br/privacy-facebook/), [Portuguese (Portugal)](http://www.topeleven.com/pt-pt/privacy-facebook/), [Serbian](http://www.topeleven.com/sr/privacy-facebook/), [Thai](http://www.topeleven.com/th/privacy-facebook/), [Turkish](http://www.topeleven.com/tr/privacy-facebook/)
